iqos.com 2005-12-12

# Packeter > Company > Board

Privacy Policy

This document sets forth the Packeteer Online Privacy Policy (the "Privacy Policy") for this Web site (the "Site"). If you have objections to the Privacy Policy, you should not access or use this Site.

**Information Collection**  
Packeteer deems privacy a central issue of Internet use. Packeteer attempts to have reasonable policy measures in place to assure the anonymity of visitors to the Packeteer web site. Packeteer feels as part of responsible disclosure that Packeteer web site users are aware of what information is being logged. 

To maintain and improve site quality and integrity, IP addresses are logged (the Internet Protocol addresses of computers). This log is a standard method of reporting to statistically find out which parts of our web site are visited and how long visitors spend there. We also log the type of browser and operating system you are using. We do not link IP addresses to personally identifiable information. 

Like many other commercial web sites, the Packeteer web site may use a standard technology called a "cookie" to collect information about how you use the site. Cookies were originally designed to help a web site distinguish a user's browser as a previous visitor and thus save and remember any preferences that may have been set while the user was browsing the site. A cookie is a small string of text that a web site can send to your browser. A cookie cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive, pass on computer viruses, or capture your e-mail address. Currently, web sites use cookies to enhance the user's visit; in general, cookies can securely store a user's ID and password, personalize home pages, identify which parts of a site have been visited or keep track of selections in a "shopping cart." It is possible to set your browser to inform you when a cookie is being placed -- this way, you have the opportunity to decide whether to accept the cookie. 

At times we may request that you voluntarily supply us with personal information, such as your e-mail address, for purposes such as corresponding with us, registering at a site, registering a new product, or participating in an online survey. 

**Information Use**  
When you supply Packeteer with your personal information, we may use the information to learn more about you so that we can develop better products and services or use the information, sharing it with our business partners, to inform you about new products, services and offers that may be of interest to you.

**Declining E-mail Offers**  
Although most customers tell us they appreciate receiving notice of these opportunities, we recognize the importance of providing you with choices. At any time after receiving an e-mail offer from Packeteer, you may request to discontinue receiving these offers. All e-mail offers that you receive from Packeteer will tell you how to decline further e-mail offers. Our partners may have different policies. 

Packeteer, Inc.'s privacy policy is subject to change at any time and without notice.
